{
    "subject": "resource/Vassmol\u00f6sa",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Sweden",
    "human_readable": "Vassmol\u00f6sa is from Sweden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9763256907463074,
            "question": "Is Vassmol\u00f6sa Swedish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9162633419036865,
            "question": "What can be inferred from the fact that Vassmol\u00f6sa is from Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8924374580383301,
            "question": "Where is Vassmol\u00f6sa from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7785129547119141,
            "question": "What country is Vassmol\u00f6sa associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6739881634712219,
            "question": "Could Vassmol\u00f6sa be a place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.609224259853363,
            "question": "How is Vassmol\u00f6sa significant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.595541775226593,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about Vassmol\u00f6sa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5772464871406555,
            "question": "What kind of information do we have about Vassmol\u00f6sa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5214748978614807,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Vassmol\u00f6sa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5081502199172974,
            "question": "Is there more to learn about Vassmol\u00f6sa?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vassmol\u00f6sa is from Sweden.",
            "html": "dbpedia_325_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything else about Vassmol\u00f6sa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_325_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of information do we have about Vassmol\u00f6sa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_325_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about Vassmol\u00f6sa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_325_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_325_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Vassmol\u00f6sa is located in Kalmar, Sweden, and provide geographical coordinates (56\u00b0 36' 0\" North, 16\u00b0 10' 0\" East) for Vassmol\u00f6sa, which further confirms its location in Sweden."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Vassmol\u00f6sa is from Sweden.\" Specifically, multiple sources indicate that Vassmol\u00f6sa is located in Kalmar Kommun, which is part of Kalmar Lan, Sweden."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}